This XML file does not appear to have any style information associated with it. The document tree is shown below.
<rss xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>MyJobMag Job Feed</title>
<link>https://www.myjobmag.co.ke</link>
<ttl>10</ttl>
<description>MyJobMag, Your Favourite Jobs Website</description>
<lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:04:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
<language>en</language>

<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[ Sales Executive at Watu Credit Limited ]]>
</title>
<industry>
<![CDATA[ NGO / Non-Profit Associations ]]>
</industry>
<position>
<![CDATA[ Sales Executive ]]>
</position>
<company>
<![CDATA[ Born Free Foundation ]]>
</company>
<location>
<![CDATA[ Nairobi ]]>
</location>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.myjobmag.co.ke/a_fields.php?id=882518 ]]>
</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">
<![CDATA[ https://www.myjobmag.co.ke/a_fields.php?id=882518 ]]>
</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 12:43:23 GMT</pubDate>
<expiryDate/>
<description>
<![CDATA[ Watu Credit Limited is a dynamic and fast-growing non-bank finance company. Watu Credit Limited harnesses technology to offer unsecured lending, primarily via mobile services. We aim to become the leading African provider of a broad set of inclusive financial products, delivered through technology in a fast, efficient and professional manner. What you will do: Identify and recruit new customers to ensure achievement of new customer targets and revenue. Recommend and execute approved activations and promotional activities with assigned regions; managing discretionary giveaways to ensure optimum return on investment. Communicate Watu Simu activities and updates to dealerships and Watu customers in a timely manner. Build and maintain strong working relationships with dealership managers and store staff to support retention Conduct market sensing and provide continuous feedback and recommend solutions within the designated region. Ensure accurate pricing, promotional pricing, competitor pricing of all products across retail shops. Identify customer and dealership training needs and implement training programs to promote sales and an understanding of processes. Collect feedback from customer complaints, queries and requests ensuring effective resolution through relevant channels. Provide timely reports on regional dealership performance and identify key performance indicators to increase sell out. Monitor store capacity, stock status and in-store pricing for appropriate execution of sales. Negotiate prime&nbsp; product display space to maximize on visibility of Watu Simu retail elements Monitor display areas for all dealerships to ensure compliance with brand guidelines on display assets on any other applicable guidelines.&nbsp; Identify in-store cross merchandising opportunities with OEM partners to enhance upselling against targets Supervise, appraise, train and support direct reports in delivering sales targets&nbsp; Execute effective route planning, objectivity and compliance for the team. KPIs: Deliver set sales targets against target Deliver set onboarding targets. Deliver off rate targets. Timely sales, customer feedback and marketing sensing reports within set timelines and templates What we are looking for: Diploma in marketing from or other applicable field from a recognisable institution. At least 4 years&rsquo; experience in sales, account management or related field preferably in the telecommunication or IT industry, with at least 1 year of experience leading teams. Technical aptitude and familiarity with various mobile phone models and phone issues. Proficiency with Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint). Knowledge of asset financing is an added advantage. Proven track record of integrity while managing business transactions. Ability to quickly strike rapport&nbsp; and build meaningful and lasting business relationships Strong sales and marketing skills with a focus on closing sales. Good planning, organization, and analytical skills. Effective communicator (verbal and written). A keen eye for detail. ]]>
</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[ Business Development Officers - Iten at Newark Frontiers ]]>
</title>
<industry>
<![CDATA[ NGO / Non-Profit Associations ]]>
</industry>
<position>
<![CDATA[ Business Development Officers - Iten ]]>
</position>
<company>
<![CDATA[ Action Aid ]]>
</company>
<location>
<![CDATA[ Elgeyo Marakwet ]]>
</location>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.myjobmag.co.ke/a_fields.php?id=882514 ]]>
</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">
<![CDATA[ https://www.myjobmag.co.ke/a_fields.php?id=882514 ]]>
</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 12:38:08 GMT</pubDate>
<expiryDate/>
<description>
<![CDATA[ Newark Capital is a credit lending company aiming to provide instant access to loans for SMEs. We are on a mission to provide instant loans to small businesses: ensuring accessibility, affordability, value and customer experience. Newark capital is headquartered in Kikuyu Town with offices in Ng&oacute;ng, Dagoreti, Ruiru, Wangige, Kikuyu, Limuru, Kiambu and Juja.Responsibilities: Loan disbursement, collections, and customer acquisition Market research and competitor analysis Client engagement and business growth strategies Reporting and data management Why Apply? Gain practical experience in sales and microfinance Career growth with hands-on mentorship Build a strong professional network Work in a dynamic and supportive environment ]]>
</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[ Business Development Officers - Rongo at Newark Frontiers ]]>
</title>
<industry>
<![CDATA[ NGO / Non-Profit Associations ]]>
</industry>
<position>
<![CDATA[ Business Development Officers - Rongo ]]>
</position>
<company>
<![CDATA[ ICS- SP Africa ]]>
</company>
<location>
<![CDATA[ Migori ]]>
</location>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.myjobmag.co.ke/a_fields.php?id=882512 ]]>
</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">
<![CDATA[ https://www.myjobmag.co.ke/a_fields.php?id=882512 ]]>
</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 12:38:08 GMT</pubDate>
<expiryDate/>
<description>
<![CDATA[ Newark Capital is a credit lending company aiming to provide instant access to loans for SMEs. We are on a mission to provide instant loans to small businesses: ensuring accessibility, affordability, value and customer experience. Newark capital is headquartered in Kikuyu Town with offices in Ng&oacute;ng, Dagoreti, Ruiru, Wangige, Kikuyu, Limuru, Kiambu and Juja.Responsibilities: Loan disbursement, collections, and customer acquisition Market research and competitor analysis Client engagement and business growth strategies Reporting and data management Why Apply? Gain practical experience in sales and microfinance Career growth with hands-on mentorship Build a strong professional network Work in a dynamic and supportive environment ]]>
</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[ Business Development Officers - Matunda at Newark Frontiers ]]>
</title>
<industry>
<![CDATA[ NGO / Non-Profit Associations ]]>
</industry>
<position>
<![CDATA[ Business Development Officers - Matunda ]]>
</position>
<company>
<![CDATA[ Triggerise (Tiko) ]]>
</company>
<location>
<![CDATA[ Uasin Gishu ]]>
</location>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.myjobmag.co.ke/a_fields.php?id=882508 ]]>
</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">
<![CDATA[ https://www.myjobmag.co.ke/a_fields.php?id=882508 ]]>
</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 12:38:08 GMT</pubDate>
<expiryDate/>
<description>
<![CDATA[ Newark Capital is a credit lending company aiming to provide instant access to loans for SMEs. We are on a mission to provide instant loans to small businesses: ensuring accessibility, affordability, value and customer experience. Newark capital is headquartered in Kikuyu Town with offices in Ng&oacute;ng, Dagoreti, Ruiru, Wangige, Kikuyu, Limuru, Kiambu and Juja.Responsibilities: Loan disbursement, collections, and customer acquisition Market research and competitor analysis Client engagement and business growth strategies Reporting and data management Why Apply? Gain practical experience in sales and microfinance Career growth with hands-on mentorship Build a strong professional network Work in a dynamic and supportive environment ]]>
</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[ Audiology Consultant at IQVIA ]]>
</title>
<industry>
<![CDATA[ NGO / Non-Profit Associations ]]>
</industry>
<position>
<![CDATA[ Audiology Consultant ]]>
</position>
<company>
<![CDATA[ International Organization for Migration (IOM) ]]>
</company>
<location>
<![CDATA[ Nairobi ]]>
</location>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.myjobmag.co.ke/a_fields.php?id=882496 ]]>
</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">
<![CDATA[ https://www.myjobmag.co.ke/a_fields.php?id=882496 ]]>
</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 12:37:08 GMT</pubDate>
<expiryDate/>
<description>
<![CDATA[ IQVIA, formerly Quintiles and IMS Health, Inc.,is an American multinational company serving the combined industries of health information technology and clinical research. It is a provider of biopharmaceutical development and commercial outsourcing services, focused primarily on Phase I-IV clinical trials and associated laboratory and analytical services, including consulting services. It has a network of more than 58,000 employees in more than 100 countries.As of 2017, IQVIA was reported to be one of the world&#39;s largest contract research organizations The Audiology Consultant will provide expert audiological services, ensuring high-quality care and support for patients. This role involves conducting hearing assessments, diagnosing auditory conditions, and recommending appropriate treatments. The consultant will work closely with other healthcare professionals to deliver comprehensive care and improve patient outcomes. Key Responsibilities: Conduct comprehensive hearing assessments and diagnostic evaluations. Interpret audiometric test results and diagnose auditory conditions. Develop and implement individualized treatment plans for patients with hearing impairments. Provide counselling and education to patients and their families regarding hearing loss and treatment options. Fit, adjust, and maintain hearing aids and other auditory devices. Collaborate with other healthcare professionals to ensure integrated patient care. Stay updated with the latest advancements in audiology and incorporate best practices into patient care. Maintain accurate and detailed patient records in compliance with healthcare regulations. Participate in community outreach programs to raise awareness about hearing health. Qualifications: Master&#39;s degree in Audiology or a related field. Valid state licensure or certification in Audiology. Experience in clinical audiology. Strong knowledge of audiometric testing and hearing aid technology. Excellent communication and interpersonal skills. Ability to work independently and as part of a multidisciplinary team. Compassionate and patient-centred approach to care. ]]>
</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[ Quality Advisor, Outreach Administration Office at Aga Khan University Hospital ]]>
</title>
<industry>
<![CDATA[ ICT / Telecommunication ]]>
</industry>
<position>
<![CDATA[ Quality Advisor, Outreach Administration Office ]]>
</position>
<company>
<![CDATA[ Cellulant Corporation ]]>
</company>
<location>
<![CDATA[ Nairobi ]]>
</location>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.myjobmag.co.ke/a_fields.php?id=882098 ]]>
</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">
<![CDATA[ https://www.myjobmag.co.ke/a_fields.php?id=882098 ]]>
</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 07:50:03 GMT</pubDate>
<expiryDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</expiryDate>
<description>
<![CDATA[ Aga Khan University Hospitals in Karachi, Pakistan and Nairobi, Kenya are private, not-for-profit institutions providing high quality health care. The Main Hospitals serve as the principal sites for clinical training for the University's Medical Colleges and Schools of Nursing and Midwifery in Pakistan and East Africa. Our Vision of Aga Khan University Hospital, Nairobi is to be the premier, tertiary, teaching and referral health care facility in sub-Saharan Africa. &acirc;&euro;&lsaquo;For over fifty years, Aga Khan University Hospital, Nairobi (AKUH) has been taking care of families in East Africa. As a private, not-for-profit hospital, we strive to provide access to quality healthcare to all who need it. At AKUH, patients are our first priority. Our team of medical professionals, faculty and staff are here to provide you and your loved ones with the highest standards of healthcare. We are committed to working together to ensure that you and your family receive outstanding medical services, first-rate facilities and compassionate care. The Aga Khan University Hospital, Nairobi has set the standard for comprehensive healthcare and modern medical education in East Africa. Our dedicated staff, advanced facilities and state-of-the-art technologies have earned the hospital great reputation as a leading medical institution and teaching hospital in the region, and beyond. Patients benefit from our unique team-based approach to car&acirc;&euro;&lsaquo;e, which enables you to benefit from the diverse expertise of our entire team of medical professionals. As the teaching hospital for Aga Khan University&rsquo;s Medical College and School of Nursing and Midwifery, we practice an evidence-based approach to medicine, driven by the cutting-edge research conducted by our experienced faculty members. Our approach to care is guided by our core principles of Quality, Access, Impact and Relevance.&acirc;&euro;&lsaquo;Responsibilities: Coordinate development/review of quality and patient safety policies, procedures, and processes Guide the interpretation and implementation of developed policies and procedures in the context of the quality and patient safety framework Constantly be involved in the training and communication of quality and patient safety issues and standards/best practice throughout the assigned areas Review accreditation and regulatory agencies survey /internal quality audit findings and support the development and implementation of corrective/preventive action plans to address non-compliance Direct and support the collection, measurement and presentation of data required for monitoring and improving quality and patient safety Lead Outreach Division in conducting Root Cause Analysis (RCA) for sentinel and adverse events Identify opportunities for Continuous Quality Improvement and support the implementation of CQI activities in Outreach Division Support clinic leaders in identification of relevant utilization management indicators Create department and physician-based data bases for identified utilization management indicators Continuously audit compliance with the quality and safety program in assigned areas Coordinate closure of matters arising from physician feedback for improved physician satisfaction and participation Provide clinical support to corporate clients via care managers Requirements: Minimum of an undergraduate degree in a Medical/clinical field; a Master&rsquo;s degree in Business or Health related field preferred. Health Management background would be an added advantage Three or more years&rsquo; experience in direct and indirect clinical care activities in a healthcare institution In-depth understanding of good clinical practice requirements Have strong experience and knowledge of clinical monitoring functions with knowledge of clinical research Excellent problem-solving skills and the ability to manage multiple tasks Excellent data analytical and presentation skills Excellent communication and interpersonal skills ]]>
</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[ Strategic Negotiator, Network Infrastructure, Sub-Saharan Africa at Google ]]>
</title>
<industry>
<![CDATA[ NGO / Non-Profit Associations ]]>
</industry>
<position>
<![CDATA[ Strategic Negotiator, Network Infrastructure, Sub-Saharan Africa ]]>
</position>
<company>
<![CDATA[ Basic Needs Basic Rights ]]>
</company>
<location>
<![CDATA[ Nairobi ]]>
</location>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.myjobmag.co.ke/a_fields.php?id=882090 ]]>
</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">
<![CDATA[ https://www.myjobmag.co.ke/a_fields.php?id=882090 ]]>
</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 07:48:57 GMT</pubDate>
<expiryDate/>
<description>
<![CDATA[ Google is an American multinational technology company specializing in Internet-related services and products that include online advertising technologies, search, cloud computing, software, and hardware.Minimum qualifications: Bachelor&#39;s degree or equivalent practical experience. 6 years of experience negotiating and structuring agreements or leading business development. Experience in performing data-driven network availability and resiliency analysis. Experience managing and partnering with partners to create relationships and business outcomes and in growing partners businesses. Experience with network capacity planning. Preferred qualifications: Experience with strategic negotiations or business development in obtaining services from high-technology providers in collocation data centers, collocation data center construction, collocation data center equipment, dark fiber, network transport, bilateral terrestrial/undersea interconnects, and IT services. Ability to discuss complex agreements with vendors, partners, and suppliers. Excellent financial skills including network present value calculations, agreement structuring, and return on investment analysis. Responsibilities Secure partnerships and business agreements with suppliers, vendors, and other stakeholders to ensure we deliver the best possible solutions to the customers and users. Build and cultivate relationships with key executives in the African technology ecosystem to foster collaboration and drive mutual success. Drive Growth to the strategic growth of our network infrastructure in Africa and help us expand our reach and impact. ]]>
</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[ Cloud Support Engineer - Networking (NDev), Support Engineering at Amazon ]]>
</title>
<industry>
<![CDATA[ Consulting ]]>
</industry>
<position>
<![CDATA[ Cloud Support Engineer - Networking (NDev), Support Engineering ]]>
</position>
<company>
<![CDATA[ Kelly ]]>
</company>
<location>
<![CDATA[ Nairobi ]]>
</location>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.myjobmag.co.ke/a_fields.php?id=882087 ]]>
</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">
<![CDATA[ https://www.myjobmag.co.ke/a_fields.php?id=882087 ]]>
</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 07:47:01 GMT</pubDate>
<expiryDate/>
<description>
<![CDATA[ We embrace new ways of doing things, make decisions quickly, and are not afraid to fail. We have the scope and capabilities of a large company, and the spirit and heart of a small one.Key job responsibilities Your day as a Cloud Support Engineer will include, but not be limited to, the following activities: You will be primarily responsible for solving customer&rsquo;s cases through a variety of contact channels (telephone, email, and web/live chat), applying advanced troubleshooting techniques to provide tailored solutions and working with them to dive deep into the root cause of an issue. You will drive initiatives that improve support related processes and our customers&rsquo; experience. These can include tutorials, how-to videos, technical articles, trainings, among others. You will leverage your customer support experience to provide feedback to internal AWS teams on how to improve our services, and work on critical, highly complex customer problems that may span multiple AWS services. You will be continuously learning ground-breaking technologies, and developing new technical skills and other professional competencies. You will act as interviewer in hiring processes, and coach/mentor new team members. BASIC QUALIFICATIONS 1+ years of software development, or 1+ years of technical support experience Experience troubleshooting and debugging technical systems Experience in systems administration (Linux Windows OS, IP tables, Windows Firewall, NAT) and network administration (IPsec/SSL VPN, BGP, Routing and Switching, TCP/IP) as well as troubleshooting tools like traceroute, mtr, ping, iperf, dig/nslookup, cURL, tcpdump/wireshark. PREFERRED QUALIFICATIONS Knowledge or experience with configuring and supporting devices such as Cisco, Juniper, Fortinet, SonicWALL, Checkpoint, Palo Alto, etc. Understanding of cloud computing concepts and/or experience with any cloud platforms (AWS, Azure, Google Cloud). Knowledge of security concepts/best practices in securing application architectures from external threats. ]]>
</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[ Technical Account Manager at Baran Telecom Networks Kenya Limited ]]>
</title>
<industry>
<![CDATA[ ICT / Telecommunication ]]>
</industry>
<position>
<![CDATA[ Technical Account Manager ]]>
</position>
<company>
<![CDATA[ ALX ]]>
</company>
<location>
<![CDATA[ Nairobi ]]>
</location>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.myjobmag.co.ke/a_fields.php?id=882063 ]]>
</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">
<![CDATA[ https://www.myjobmag.co.ke/a_fields.php?id=882063 ]]>
</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 07:35:21 GMT</pubDate>
<expiryDate/>
<description>
<![CDATA[ Baran Telecom Networks (BTN) is a leading Telecom and Software solutions company providing innovative digital solutions through integrated emerging technologies such as Digital Platforms, Big Data, IoT, AI, and SDx. The Technical Account Manager is responsible for managing and maintaining strong relationships with key clients, providing technical expertise, ensuring successful solution implementation, handling account management, payment collections, and client review meetings. This role requires a strong background ability to bridge the gap between technical solutions and customer needs. Responsibilities: Serve as the primary technical contact for key clients, ensuring their needs are met with appropriate solutions. Collaborate with the sales and business development team to identify business opportunities and provide technical insights for proposal development. Work closely with the engineering and product/service teams to communicate customer feedback and drive improvements in service delivery. Work closely with the Program Manager to manage project timelines, deliverables, and client expectations to ensure successful implementation of projects. Ensure customer satisfaction through regular check-ins, proactive communication, and identifying areas for improvement. Follow up on and collect payments from clients for delivered projects or completed milestones. Attend meetings with clients to discuss project progress, technical solutions, and business needs. Prepare and deliver technical reports, documentation, and client presentations. Requirements Minimum Educational Qualifications: Bachelor&rsquo;s degree in electrical &amp; electronics engineering, Telecommunication Engineering, or a related technical field. Minimum Previous Experience: 4+ Years of experience in B2B &amp; B2G Account Management, technical consulting, or telecom infrastructure solutions. Proven experience in technical sales and account management. Strong understanding of telecommunications, networking, power systems, or related technologies. Ability to communicate complex technical concepts to both technical and non-technical audiences. ]]>
</description>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>